Michael Munn

Cloud Systems Software Engineer at DXC Technology

michael.munn@gmail.com

Summary

Experienced Systems Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Java, Java Message Service (JMS), Servlets, AWS, Private Clouds, and Hybrid Cloud. Strong engineering professional with a BS focused in Computer Science from Cal State East Bay.

Experience

Cloud Systems Software Engineer at DXC Technology

April 2017 - Present

Provided code fixes for the Eucalyptus Hybrid Cloud system as they related to customer and AWS compatibility issues in JAVA, C/C++, Python and Groovy. See Eucalyptus Experience.

Cloud Systems Software Engineer at Hewlett Packard Enterprise

November 2014 - April 2017 (2 years 6 months)

Provided code fixes for the Eucalyptus Hybrid Cloud system as they related to customer and AWS compatibility issues in JAVA, C/C++, Python and Groovy. See Eucalyptus Experience.

Cloud Systems Software Engineer at Eucalyptus Systems Inc.

April 2012 - November 2014 (2 years 8 months)

Provided code fixes for the Eucalyptus Hybrid Cloud system as they related to customer and AWS compatibility issues in JAVA, C/C++, Python and Groovy. Developed automated test cases/suites against the Eucalyptus system using both Python and Boto. I also Developed and provided training for frontline Support engineers on various Eucalyptus services including, EC2, S3, IAM, VPC, Autoscaling, Cloudformation, Cloudwatch and SWF.

Principle Member Of Technical Staff at Oracle Corporation at Oracle

February 2010 - April 2012 (2 years 3 months)

Sustaining of Both Weblogic and Glassfish application servers as well as Coherence distributed data Grid. I provided code fixes in Java for both Application Servers and created automated test cases using Junit for all fixes that were integrated. I also provided support and training to front-line Support engineers.

Staff Engineer at Sun Microsystems

September 1998 - February 2010 (11 years 6 months)

I Was the US Sustaining technical lead. I provided code fixes for the Glassfish application Server, iPlanet Application Server and iPlanet Web Server. I created automated test cases using Junit for all fixes that were integrated. I also provided mentoring, support and training for frontline Support engineers

Support/Sustaining Engineer

November 1996 - September 1998 (1 year 11 months)

Support and Sustaining of the NetDynamics application server.

Resolved customer issues by providing workarounds or code fixes.

Education

California State University - East Bay

BS, Computer Science, 1996 - 1998

College of San Mateo

AS, Computer Science, 1994 - 1996

Michael Munn

Cloud Systems Software Engineer at DXC Technology

michael.munn@gmail.com



Contact Michael on LinkedIn